連絡先

www.linkedin.com/in/cherry-o-210924ab (LinkedIn)

トップスキル

Presentations
Technical Sales Presentations
Leadership

Languages

Tagalog (Native or Bilingual)
English (Native or Bilingual)
Spanish (Professional Working)
Japanese (Full Professional)
Korean (Elementary)
French (Elementary)

Certifications

TOEIC 985/990

DELE B2 (Diplomas of Spanish as a Foreign Language)

JLPT N2 (Japanese Language Proficiency Test)

Master of Business Administration

BJT N2 (Business Japanese Proficiency Test)

Publications

The Vanishing of e-wastes in the Philippines

Cherry O.

Associate (Marketing & Sales Specialist) at McKinsey | MBA at INSEAD

広域東京エリア

キャリアサマリ

I have more than 6 years of experience bridging the needs of customers across Asia Pacific, Latin America and Europe, with the expertise on technology from Japan. A true believer of continuous improvement, I pursued an MBA at INSEAD where I enhanced my leadership skills and learned various business tools that could contribute to the overall growth of businesses. Currently, I am an Associate (Marketing & Sales Specialist) at McKinsey & Company in Tokyo, Japan.

職歴

McKinsey & Company Associate (Marketing & Sales Specialist) 2019年9月 - Present (5年 10ヶ月) Within 23 wards, Tokyo, Japan

- Served global companies on commercial transformations across consumer
- packaged goods industry
 Focus on analytics-driven B2C pricing, agile M&S transformation, and
- Focus on analytics-driven B2C pricing, agile M&S transformation, and consumer insights in recent engagements

INSEAD

MBA Graduate Student 2018年8月 - 2019年7月 (1年)

Fontainebleau, France

Toshiba 6年 2ヶ月

International Sales Expert 2017年4月 - 2018年8月 (1年 5ヶ月)

Kawasaki, Kanagawa, Japan

Strategic Planner 2016年11月 - 2017年3月 (5ヶ月)

日本 神奈川県 川崎市

Business Planning Department of the Industrial Systems Division
-In charge of the strategic planning for industrial products which include motors, drives, batteries, measuring instruments, and others.

Business Specialist 2016年4月 - 2016年10月 (7ヶ月)

Mexico City Area, Mexico

Marketing Division

- Specialized in overseas business development of infrastructure-related products such as power plants, energy storage system, radar, airport navigation aids, and other electric components.
- -Overseas assignment to Toshiba de Mexico for 6 months under the Emerging Countries' Business Specialist Program

Business Development Associate 2015年4月 - 2016年3月 (1年)

日本 神奈川県 川崎市

Global Business Development Division

- -Coordinated the cross-selling of infrastructure-related products.
- -Developed new accounts in the North America and South America region.
- -Led the overseas expansion of a disaster prevention system for countries in the Asia-Pacific that are heavily affected by meteorological disasters.

Sales Engineer 2012年7月 - 2015年3月 (2年 9ヶ月)

Tokyo, Japan

Instrumentation and Control Equipment Department

- In charge of the overseas sales and business development of X-ray, Gamma-ray and laser light measuring instruments for metal industries in Asia and Europe.
- Prepared technical and sales proposals according to customer's specifications, and further headed negotiations and kick-off meetings.

学歴

INSEAD

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Class of July 2019 · (2018 - 2019)

Ateneo de Manila University

Bachelor's Degree, Chemistry, Materials Science and Engineering · (2007 - 2012)

Quezon City Science High School High School, Science · (2002 - 2007)
